<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Equinix News Feed</title>
        <link>https://forum.equinix.com/rss/news</link>
        <atom:link href="https://forum.equinix.com/rss/news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <description/>
        <item>
            <title>Bloomberg Tech Disruptors - Equinix: Interconnecting the World via Digital Infrastructure</title>
            <link>https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/equinix-interconnecting-the-world-via-digital/id1621165150?i=1000598549598</link>
            <guid>https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/equinix-interconnecting-the-world-via-digital/id1621165150?i=1000598549598</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Equinix CEO Charles Meyers joins Bloomberg to discuss trends in the data center market that underpin Equinix's market-leading operating performance. As the world shifts more and more towards digital, Equinix sits in the middle, providing a valuable service to customers needing connectivity. During the conversation we discuss the importance of the cloud, a focus on ecosystems, a shift toward sustainability, global expansion, and the heating of Olympic swimming pools in Paris. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2023-02-09T00:00:00-05:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bloomberg Radio - Corporate Leadership, Markets, and Nonprofits</title>
            <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2022-12-01/corporate-leadership-markets-and-nonprofits-podcast</link>
            <guid>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/audio/2022-12-01/corporate-leadership-markets-and-nonprofits-podcast</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Charles Meyers, CEO at Equinix, joins Bloomberg to discuss digital infrastructure and how it’s operating amid varying economic headwinds in tech. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CNBC - Demand remains ‘strong and inelastic’ for our business, says Equinix CEO</title>
            <link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/11/03/demand-remains-strong-and-inelastic-for-our-business-says-equinix-ceo.html</link>
            <guid>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/11/03/demand-remains-strong-and-inelastic-for-our-business-says-equinix-ceo.html</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Equinix CEO Charles Meyers joins ‘TechCheck’ to discuss Meyers optimism regarding pricing power, why customer demand won’t taper with higher prices and if Equinix is more cyclical than initially imagined. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-11-03T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hong Kong Economic Times - Technology company launches global internship programme to attract talents from diversified backgrounds</title>
            <link>https://paper.hket.com/article/3384759/%E7%A7%91%E4%BC%81%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E5%AF%A6%E7%BF%92%E7%94%9F%E8%A8%88%E5%8A%83 %E7%99%BC%E6%8E%98%E5%A4%9A%E5%85%83%E5%B0%88%E6%89%8D</link>
            <guid>https://paper.hket.com/article/3384759/%E7%A7%91%E4%BC%81%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E5%AF%A6%E7%BF%92%E7%94%9F%E8%A8%88%E5%8A%83 %E7%99%BC%E6%8E%98%E5%A4%9A%E5%85%83%E5%B0%88%E6%89%8D</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Hong Kong's workforce had contracted by about 140,000 over the past two years. Equinix believes that the unique workplace culture of a company would attract young talents aged 20-30. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-10-27T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The West Australian - Prime Minister Anthony Albanese and Premier Mark McGowan turn on $300m Oman-Australia Cable</title>
            <link>https://thewest.com.au/business/trade/prime-minister-anthony-albanese-and-premier-mark-mcgowan-turn-on-300m-oman-australia-cable-c-8633624</link>
            <guid>https://thewest.com.au/business/trade/prime-minister-anthony-albanese-and-premier-mark-mcgowan-turn-on-300m-oman-australia-cable-c-8633624</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Guy Danskine, Managing Director, Equinix Australia talks about the rapidly growing need for subsea cables to provide a much faster and more efficient pathway for customers to send data across the world. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-10-23T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Data Center Dynamics - Escaping Ukraine: Data migration during an invasion</title>
            <link>https://www.datacenterdynamics.com/en/analysis/escaping-ukraine-data-migration-during-an-invasion/</link>
            <guid>https://www.datacenterdynamics.com/en/analysis/escaping-ukraine-data-migration-during-an-invasion/</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ This article covers how Wise escaped Russia\'s war in Ukraine with the help of Equinix Metal and others ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-10-18T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Forbes - Equinix Working To Close Digital Divide</title>
            <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomcoughlin/2022/10/10/equinix-working-to-close-digital-divide-and-minio-reaches-1b-downloads/?ss=enterprisetech&sh=6ac3538913c5</link>
            <guid>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomcoughlin/2022/10/10/equinix-working-to-close-digital-divide-and-minio-reaches-1b-downloads/?ss=enterprisetech&sh=6ac3538913c5</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Forbes interviewed key Equinix execs on the launch of a global foundation focused on the advancement of digital inclusion. The Equinix Foundation will provide funding to organizations working to ensure equitable and inclusive access to technology, connectivity and education. It will also assess opportunities in environmental sustainability, an area of strategic importance for the company. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-10-10T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CNBC - Equinix plays a critical role in helping companies move to hybrid and multi cloud, says CEO</title>
            <link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/08/04/equinix-plays-a-critical-role-in-helping-companies-move-to-hybrid-and-multi-cloud-says-ceo.html</link>
            <guid>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/08/04/equinix-plays-a-critical-role-in-helping-companies-move-to-hybrid-and-multi-cloud-says-ceo.html</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Charles Meyers, Equinix CEO, joins ‘TechCheck’ to discuss why big companies should use outside data centers, the amount of capital investment necessary for data center valuations to make sense and more. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-08-04T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kalkine TV - Trends in Digital Future of Leadership</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2tnEpaTJjTo&t=3s</link>
            <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2tnEpaTJjTo&t=3s</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Guy Danskine, Managing Director, Equinix Australia talks about the latest findings in the Global Tech Trends Survey and the importance of enabling digital transformation. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Les Echos - Interview: \"The cloud market will be very resilient in the face of inflation,\" says Equinix CEO</title>
            <link>https://www.lesechos.fr/tech-medias/hightech/le-marche-du-cloud-sera-tres-resilient-face-a-linflation-dit-le-patron-dequinix-1780024</link>
            <guid>https://www.lesechos.fr/tech-medias/hightech/le-marche-du-cloud-sera-tres-resilient-face-a-linflation-dit-le-patron-dequinix-1780024</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Equinix CEO, Charles Meyers, discusses the company’s anticipated growth in line with increased digital demand, highlighting Equinix’s plans to invest a billion dollars in France over the next five years. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hong Kong Economic Journal - Equinix Partners with HKBN and OpenRice to further expand into other Asia-Pacific markets</title>
            <link>http://startupbeat.hkej.com/?p=121691</link>
            <guid>http://startupbeat.hkej.com/?p=121691</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Equinix, OpenRice, and HKBN Enterprise Solutions (HKBN) are partnering to further enhance infrastructure for OpenRice’s all-encompassing online-to-offline (O2O) foodtech services platform. The collaboration paves the way for OpenRice’s booking service to further expand into other Asia-Pacific (APAC) markets beyond Hong Kong, including Singapore, Taiwan, Thailand and Japan. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-07-22T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Lianhe Zaobao - New local data centers must meet stricter green standards</title>
            <link>https://www.zaobao.com.sg/news/singapore/story20220721-1294858</link>
            <guid>https://www.zaobao.com.sg/news/singapore/story20220721-1294858</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ The article was based on an interview that Yee May Leong did with Lianhe Zaobao in response to stricter green regulations for data centers implemented by the Singapore government. She shared that Equinix\'s digital infrastructure empowers public and private organizations with the capabilities necessary for innovation, participation and success in the digital economy. This is crucial as enterprises in Singapore continue their drive towards digital transformation, solidifying Singapore\'s status as South-east Asia\'s premier business and technology hub. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-07-21T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Business Times - Data centre pilot to set higher efficiency standards, give operators longer leases</title>
            <link>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/companies-markets/data-centre-pilot-to-set-higher-efficiency-standards-give-operators-longer-leases</link>
            <guid>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/companies-markets/data-centre-pilot-to-set-higher-efficiency-standards-give-operators-longer-leases</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ The article highlighted the interview with Yee May Leong regarding the recent announcement from the Economic Development Board and Infocomm Media Development Authority on the launch of the pilot data centre call-for-application exercise. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-07-20T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Electronic Times - Web 3.0 and future of digital technology</title>
            <link>https://www.etnews.com/20220708000207</link>
            <guid>https://www.etnews.com/20220708000207</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ In this article, Managing Director of Equinix Korea Chris Jang stresses that as Web 3.0 is growing in various companies, especially in APAC, the latest digital infrastructure that provides more data storage with lower latency is needed to support the growth of new technology. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-07-10T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hong Kong Economic Times - Seven in 10 Hong Kong Businesses Plan to Expand in New Markets in the Next 12 Months</title>
            <link>https://inews.hket.com/article/3295332/</link>
            <guid>https://inews.hket.com/article/3295332/</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Equinix 2022 Global Tech Trends Survey revealed that 71% of Hong Kong respondents indicated their organization is planning to expand in the next 12 months. More than half of Hong Kong IT leaders (54%) planned to increase their investments in 5G technology, and 64% believed that IT infrastructures and systems require upgrading in order to fully capitalize on this new technology. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-07-07T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Forbes - The Digital Train Isn’t Slowing Down Anytime Soon</title>
            <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joemckendrick/2022/07/06/the-digital-train-isnt-slowing-down-anytime-soon/?sh=608b487d43fd</link>
            <guid>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joemckendrick/2022/07/06/the-digital-train-isnt-slowing-down-anytime-soon/?sh=608b487d43fd</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Forbes covered the Equinix 2022 Global Tech Trends Survey, with a focus on how companies are investing in emerging technology, specifically Web3. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-07-06T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Fortune - How Equinix is using A.I. to increase its energy efficiency</title>
            <link>https://fortune.com/videos/watch/How-Equinix-is-using-AI-to-increase-its-energy-efficiency-/3baa2d87-2fd3-4bbc-8b9a-a39a2b040a90</link>
            <guid>https://fortune.com/videos/watch/How-Equinix-is-using-AI-to-increase-its-energy-efficiency-/3baa2d87-2fd3-4bbc-8b9a-a39a2b040a90</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ CEO Charles Meyer sits down with Fortune’s Susie Gharib to discuss how Equinix is using A.I. to increase its energy efficiency ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Forbes - Sustainability Efforts At Equinix And SoftIron</title>
            <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomcoughlin/2022/05/31/sustainability-efforts-at-equinix-and-softiron/?sh=4b8d5ee13d0b</link>
            <guid>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomcoughlin/2022/05/31/sustainability-efforts-at-equinix-and-softiron/?sh=4b8d5ee13d0b</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Equinix is driving a push towards more sustainable data centers using Fuel Cells and other initiatives in its Clean Hydrogen Partnership. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-05-31T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Venturebeat - How Equinix wants the internet to be ready for the metaverse</title>
            <link>https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/how-equinix-wants-the-internet-to-be-ready-for-the-metaverse/</link>
            <guid>https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/how-equinix-wants-the-internet-to-be-ready-for-the-metaverse/</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ Venturebeat interviewed Matt George and discusses how Equinix, which has more than 240 datacenters around the world, is contemplating how to build the metaverse.\n ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-05-30T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Fortune - Equinix CEO: This data center giant does \"exceptionally well\" even in downturns</title>
            <link>https://fortune.com/videos/watch/equinix-ceo%3A-this-data-center-giant-does-%22exceptionally-well%22-even-in-downturns/3e10d64e-a96c-4739-b7cc-50d56af1e9dd?xid=soc_socialflow_twitter_FORTUNE&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=fortunemagazine&utm_source=twitter.com</link>
            <guid>https://fortune.com/videos/watch/equinix-ceo%3A-this-data-center-giant-does-%22exceptionally-well%22-even-in-downturns/3e10d64e-a96c-4739-b7cc-50d56af1e9dd?xid=soc_socialflow_twitter_FORTUNE&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=fortunemagazine&utm_source=twitter.com</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ In this video interview, CEO Charles Meyers says business is booming thanks to surge in digital transformation. ]]>
            </description>
            <PubDate>2022-05-24T00:00:00-04:00</PubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>